睡眠, 死亡的片段, 我多么憎恨它们
《猛鬼街3：梦之战》
你疯了吗  你会吵醒邻居的
Are you crazy? You'll wake up the whole neighborhood.
- 妈  - 别跟我耍嘴皮子
- Hi, Mom. - Don't "Hi, Mom," me.
你怎么还没睡  已经一点多了
What are you still doing up? It's past 1.
我想等你回来
Just thought I'd wait for you.
我回来了  你该去睡觉
Well, I'm home. Now you can get to sleep.
快点  动作快
Come on, Andale.
妈  我真的不累
Mom, I'm really not tired.
克莉丝丹  别惹我  你知道心理医生是怎么说的
Kristen, don't start with me. You know what your shrink said.
他是在胡说八道
He's full of it.
今晚我不跟你吵
I'm not gonna let you get me into an argument, not tonight.
快睡吧
Now get to sleep.
妈妈
Mom...
我还是会做恶梦
...I'm still having those awful dreams.
伊莲  波本威士忌放在哪里
Elaine, where do you keep the bourbon?
我立刻下去
Uh, I'll be right down.
- 乖女儿  我有客人  - 你不想让他久等
- Honey, I've got a guest. - And you don't wanna keep him waiting.
没错  我不想让他久等
That's right, I don't.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
一  二
One, two
佛莱迪要来抓你了
Freddy's coming for you
三  四
Three, four
锁好你的门
Better lock your door
五  六
Five, six
快去拿十字架
Grab your crucifix
七  八
Seven, eight
彻夜不眠
Gonna stay up late
九  十
Nine, ten
永远不要睡
Never sleep again
一  二
One, two
佛莱迪要来抓你了
Freddy's coming for you
三  四
Three, four
锁好你的门
Better lock your door
五  六
Five, six
快去拿十字架
Grab your crucifix
七  八
Seven, eight
彻夜不眠
Gonna stay up late
九  十
Nine, ten
嗨  你叫什么名字
Hi, what's your name?
克莉丝丹  你呢
Kristen. What's yours?
这是什么地方
What is this place?
我得走了
I gotta go now.
等一下  小妹妹  别进去
Wait, little girl, don't go in there!
小妹妹
Little girl!
Little girl?
他就是带我们来这里
This is where he takes us.
来吧  我们得走了
Come on, we're going.
佛莱迪回来了
Freddy's home.
放我下去  你弄痛我了
Put me down, you're hurting me.
克莉丝丹
Kristen!
妈
Mom?
地方新闻  又有两名青少年死亡  死因皆是自杀
...two more teenage deaths have occurred. Both suicides.
郡卫生部门官员无法解释  为什么会出现自杀风潮
County health officials are at a loss to explain this alarming trend.
一大早就听到这种新闻  不是件好事吧
Nothing like a little cheery news to start the day, huh?
没错  听我说  医生
Yeah. Say, listen, doc.
我对这些自杀案有套新理论
I got a new theory about all these suicides, right?
别对我们有所隐瞒  马克思  我们需要帮助
Don't hold back on us, Max, we need all the help we can get.
对  那是染色体的问题
Yeah, well, it's fucked up chromosomes, man.
好好想一想  他们的爸妈在六零年代猛嗑迷幻药
Think about it, all their parents dropped acid during the '60s.
这比希莫丝的理论好多了
It beats Simms' theory.
她认为这跟性爱  毒品及摇滚乐脱不了关系
She thinks it's nothing but sex, drugs and rock 'n' roll.
- 该死  那是人们活下去的力量 - 嘿
- Shit, that's what keeps people alive. - Heh.
嗨  泰纶
Hi, Taryn.
你看起来精神不太好  孩子  你有睡觉吗
You don't look so hot, kid. Are you getting some sleep?
- 应该没有  - 早安  哥登医生
- I didn't think so. - Good morning, Dr. Gordon.
早安  珍妮佛  你烫伤的地方还好吧
Good morning, Jennifer. How are the burns?
- 慢慢好了  - 伤口愈合还好吧
- Regular, menthol, ultra-light. - They're healing up nicely?
对  非常不错
Yeah, I've been good.
我什么时候能再开始抽烟
So, um, when do I get my cigarette privileges back?
别抱太大的希望
Don't hold your breath.
- 菲利普  - 医生
- Phillip. - Hey, doc.
- 他还好吧  - 冷静下来了
- How is he? - He's cooling down.
如果他继续抓狂  就必须永久隔离
If he continues having these outbursts, I'll have to have him isolated permanently.
别担心  不会那么糟糕的
Aw, don't worry, it won't come to that.
我看了新人的报告
I, uh...I read the report on the new staff member.
你觉得呢
Oh, what did you think?
老实说  我不了解
Frankly, I don't understand...
为什么研究所高材生  被当成专业人士看待
...why some grad-school superstar is being treated like a seasoned pro.
她对模式恶梦有突破性研究
She's been doing groundbreaking research on pattern nightmares.
伊莉莎白  我们不需要外力帮忙  我了解这些孩子
Elizabeth, we don't need any outside help. I know these kids.
我不需要大明星拿他们冒险
I don't want some hotshot taking chances with
只为了要发表论文
them just so she can get published.
哥登医生  希莫丝医生  请立刻到检查室
Dr. Gordon, Dr. Simms to Examination, stat.
这太夸张了  我了解我女儿
This is ridiculous. I know my own daughter.
她只是想引人注意
She's trying to get attention, that's all.
我不想配合她演出
And I'm not gonna play her games with her.
从郡综合医院转来的自杀病患
Suicide attempt from County General.
- 她叫什么名字  - 克莉丝丹  帕克
- What's her name? - Kristen Parker.
我们帮她注射镇定剂前  她本来还好好的
She was fine until we tried to sedate her.
小心  她将缝线拉掉了
Watch it, she tore her stitches out.
克莉丝丹  我们是想帮助你
Kristen, we wanna help you.
抓住她  抓住她
Hold her, hold her. Aah!
不  不  不
No, no, no.
我是哥登医生  我不会伤害你  我要帮你
I'm Dr. Gordon. I'm not gonna hurt you, I wanna help you.
- 你何不  - 不
- Why don't you... - No!
小心点  马克思
Be careful, Max.
退后  马克思
Back off, Max.
克莉丝丹  刀子放下
Kristen, put the scalpel down.
没有人会伤害你
Nobody is gonna hurt you.
五  六
Five, six
快去拿十字架
Grab your crucifix
七  八
Seven, eight
彻夜不眠
Better stay up late
九  十
Nine, ten
永远
Never, never...
永远别睡
Never sleep again.
你在哪里学会那首童谣的
Where did you learn that rhyme?
跟我谈谈那些孩子的状况
Tell me about the kids.
某方面而言  他们可说是幸存者
Well, they're survivors in a way.
他们都有严重的睡眠障碍  失眠  猝睡症跟尿床
They're all severely sleep disordered. Insomnia, narcolepsy, bed-wetting.
- 做恶梦是共同的症状  - 对
- But the nightmares are the common thread. - Right.
他们似乎有集体幻想  一个恶鬼  我不知道该如何形容
They seem to share a group delusion, a bogeyman, for lack of a better word.
他们都饱受精神折磨  想尽办法不让自己睡着
They're so traumatized, they'll do almost anything not to sleep.
是吗
Anything?
一个月前在费尔悠死了一个孩子
We lost a kid about a month ago to Fairview.
我不知道他怎么拿到刀子的
I don't know where he got the razors,
但他割下眼皮只为了不想睡着
but he cut off his eyelids to stay awake.
- 天啊  - 那些孩子都吓坏了
- Oh, God. - Shook the kids up pretty badly.
对了  你处理新来的病患很有一套
Oh, by the way, that was really great work with the new patient.
就实习生来说真的很不错
Pretty smooth for an intern.
我对模式恶梦有些经验
I have had some experience with pattern nightmares.
- 我得走了  - 好的
- I've got to get going. - Okay, well....
我来帮你捡
Let me help you with that.
- 谢谢  - 不客气
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
记得去找马克思
Now, uh, be sure that you check in with Max...
他会好好带你参观这里
...and he'll give you the whole 25-cent tour and everything.
- 好  待会儿见  - 好的
- All right, I'll see you later. - All right.
呃  汤普森小姐
Oh, um, Miss Thompson?
- 你可以叫我南希  - 好的
- You can call me Nancy. - All right.
你叫我尼尔  好吗  那首童谣是怎么一回事
You call me Neil, all right? What was that nursery rhyme all about?
孩子们会念那首童谣赶走恶鬼
That was just something that the kids say to keep the bogeyman away.
总之那是团体治疗室
Anyway, that's group therapy.
这一区专门用来做团体治疗
This whole wing is devoted to the program. Um....
我想你暂时可以用这间办公室
I guess, yeah, you can use this office for the time being, okay?
- 没问题  - 太棒了
- This will be fine. - All right, great.
周末前我会想办法  帮你找个私人办公室
Because I'll have you set up in your own space by the end of the week.
病房在这边
Um, the patients' rooms are down this way.
他是菲利普  我们都叫他游魂
This is Phillip. We call him "The Walker."
- 为什么  - 因为我会梦游
- Why is that? - Because I sleepwalk.
那很正常
Perfectly normal event...
但这里的名医  喜欢没事提出一大堆理论
...that our illustrious staff loves to theorize about endlessly.
菲利普  这位是南希
Phillip, this is Nancy.
欢迎光临蛇窟
Hi, welcome to the snake pit. Heh.
谢谢
Thanks.
非常不错
Nice work.
事实上那应该是木雕  但他们不让我用刀子
They really ought to be carved out of wood, but they won't let me have a knife.
我可能会  你知道的
I might, you know, pfft!
这个懒鬼是金凯德
Um, this lump over here, this is Kincaid.
我要你仔细看好了
Now, I want you to take a good look.
他常被关进禁闭室  你看到他的机会大概不多
He gets thrown in the quiet room so often, you probably won't see a lot of him.
对吧  小帅哥
Ain't that right, cool breeze?
对  我会那么做  只是不想常看到你的丑脸
Right, I do it so I don't have to look at your ugly face all the time.
对  我也爱你
Yeah, I love you too.
幸会
Nice meeting you.
他们都是好孩子  但别被骗了
Yeah, they're really good kids but, uh, don't let them fool you.
他们很危险  对自己跟别人都是
They're dangerous, to themselves and to each other.
嗨  乔伊
Hi, Joey.
谢谢
Why, thank you.
- 玛西  你还好吗  - 我很好
- Hey, Marcie, how you doing? - Great.
- 这些要送去C区病房  - 对
- These going to C Ward? - Yeah.
来吧  我帮你推过去
Come on, I'll walk you down.
待会儿见  乔伊
See you later, Joey.
帕克太太  克莉丝丹曾出现异常状况吗
Mrs. Parker, was Kristen acting any different?
在她企图自杀前  你有注意到不寻常的事吗
Did you notice anything strange before she made the attempt?
克莉丝丹一向怪里怪气的
Kristen specializes in strangeness.
我花了不少钱让她看精神科医生
I've spent thousands on psychiatrists.
她一直都会做恶梦吗
Did she always have nightmares?
不  没收她的信用卡后  状况才越来越糟糕
No, they've gotten worse since I took away her credit cards.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
汤普森小姐  我不知道你为什么要找我谈
Miss Thompson, I don't know what you want from me.
我只是想知道答案
Just some answers.
很多孩子都住院了  不只是克莉丝丹
There are other kids involved, not just Kristen.
他们都是好孩子  非常聪明
All good kids, smart kids.
听着  我真的很遗憾  但你才是专家  我什么都不懂
Look, I'm sorry to hear that but you're the experts on this, not me.
如果我知道发生了什么事  一定会告诉你  相信我
If I had any insight into any of this, I would share them with you, believe me.
我相信你一定会的
I'm sure you would.
对不起  我得去一趟市区
If you'll excuse me, I have to get downtown.
我需要她的一些东西
I'll need to get her things.
我把她的东西都放在行李箱里
I have them packed in a suitcase.
泰瑞莎
Theresa!
请让我自己去拿  我不介意
I'll get them, please, I don't mind.
上楼后第一个房间
It's the first door at the top of the stairs.
南希
Nancy!
不
No!
- 是你  - 天啊
- You. - Oh, my God.
快逃
Run!
快帮助我们逃出去  克莉丝丹  快一点
Get us back out, Kristen, do it now.
以前我住在这间房子里
I used to Iive in this house.
那是我梦到的房子
That's just a house I dream about.
你那样做过吗  把别人拉到你的梦中
Have you ever done that before, pull someone into your dream?
我还小的时候  应该只有四  五岁
When I was a little girl, like 4 or 5...
如果我做了恶梦  总是会把我爸拉入梦里
...if I had a nightmare, I would always bring my dad in.
恶梦总会变得比较不可怕
The dreams would always get better.
隔天他会跟我说起  他以为是他在做梦
He used to tell me about it the next day. He used to think they were his dreams.
- 哈哈 - 你何时不再那样做了
- Ha, ha. - And when did that stop?
我还小的时候
When I was still a kid.
我爸妈离婚
My folks got divorced.
过了一阵子  我以为那是我的想像
And after a while, I just thought I imagined the whole thing.
我想那不是幻想
I guess I didn't.
那是非常棒的天分
It's an amazing gift.
我梦里的那个人  他真的存在  对不对
The man in my dreams, he's real, isn't he?
他真的存在
He's real.
好吧  大家都来了  在这里我们必须直言不讳
Okay, group's in session. Straight talk only in this room.
今天我要跟大家介绍一下
Today, I'd like to start getting us acquainted...
我们的新工作人员  南希  汤普森
...with our new staff member, Nancy Thompson.
大家跟她打个招呼
Let's make her all welcome.
- 你好  南希 - 你好
- Hi, Nancy. - Hi.
- 你好  南希  - 南希
- Hi, Nancy. - Hey, Nancy.
你见过菲利普跟金凯德  当然还有克莉丝丹
Now, you've already met Phillip and Kincaid and, of course, Kristen.
其他人何不跟南希做一下自我介绍
How about the rest of you all tell Nancy something about yourselves?
威尔  从你开始好吗
Will, how about you first?
我是威尔史  坦顿  你应该看得出来  我发生了意外
Hi, I'm Will Stanton and, um, I've had a little accident, as you can see.
结果必须坐轮椅
Ended up in this chair.
意外个头啦
Accident, my ass.
我以为在这里必须直言不讳
I thought this was supposed to be straight talk in here.
他是跳楼又怎样
Hey, so he took a jump.
至少他没有跟那些流氓共用针头
At least, he wasn't sticking needles in his arm with a bunch of lowlifes.
别说了  金凯德
Save it, Kincaid.
- 珍妮佛 - 嗯哼
- Jennifer? - Um, ahem.
我是珍妮佛  考菲德
I'm Jennifer Caulfield.
离开这里后  我要到洛杉矶当演员
And, um, as soon as I get out of here, I'm going to Los Angeles to be an actress.
我要当电视明星
I'm gonna be on TV.
对  《有钱疯子的人生》
Yeah, Lifestyles of the Rich and Psychotic.
去你的
Screw you.
他是乔伊
This is Joey.
他以前在学校参加辩论社  现在话却不多
He used to be a debater in school, but now he doesn't talk much.
我是泰纶怀特
I'm Taryn White.
我会来这里  因为这里比少年感化院好
The only reason I'm in here is because it's a better deal than juvie hall...
而且我遇到一些怪事
...also, because I'm going through some very strange shit.
你的梦
Your dreams?
大家都会做恶梦
Hey, everybody has bad dreams.
我能插句话帮大家节省一下时间吗
Can I interject something here just to save us all some time?
当然可以  菲利普  说吧
Sure, Phillip, go ahead.
根据我们慈悲的医生的说法
Well, according to our kind hosts...
我们的梦是种团体精神病  像是一种温和的集体歇斯底里
...our dreams are a group psychosis, sort of a mellow mass hysteria.
没有人在乎我们彼此认识前就梦到这个家伙
The fact we dreamt about this guy before we met doesn't seem to impress anybody.
- 对  - 没错
- Yeah. - That's right.
我们是在绕圈圈  费尽心力却看不到成果
So we go in circles, making minimal progress with maximum effort.
除非认清梦境的本质  否则你是不会有任何进展的
You won't make any progress until you recognize your dreams for what they are.
它们的本质是什么
And what are they?
罪恶感的副产物
The by-products of guilt.
心理创伤  源自道德冲突跟性欲旺盛
Psychological scars, stemming from moral conflicts and overt sexuality.
太棒了  现在我的小弟弟害死我了
Oh, great, now it's my dick that's killing me.
告诉我再来会发生什么事
Tell me what's supposed to be happening again.
好吧  你会被犬魔攻击  快点
Okay, you're being attacked by the bog demon. Go ahead.
- 十四点  - 那不算数
- Uh, 14. - Doesn't count.
你得照规定来
You got to say the words.
这太蠢了
This is stupid.
快点
Oh, come on.
以精灵王子罗雷克之名  魔鬼快快退去
In the name of Lowrek, Prince of Elves, demon, begone.
太棒了  你征服了魔鬼  但你的马被困在沼泽里
Good, you conquered the demon but your horse is sinking in the bog.
你打算怎么办
What do you do?
我上床睡觉
I go to bed...
明天一早我会有新的马
...and get a new horse in the morning.
我可以拿到什么  下咒昏睡或死亡
Well, how do I score that? Enchanted slumber or death?
好  孩子们  熄灯了
All right, fellas, lights out.
- 噢  马克思  - 噢  马克思
- Oh, Max. - "Oh, Max."
你们知道规定的
You know the rules.
- 对  - 来吧  乔伊  你也一样
- Yeah. - Come on, Joey, you too.
每次我们玩得正开心
Every time we get a good game going...
- 熄灯时间就到了 - 嗯嗯
- ...it's always lights out. - Mm-hm.
好
Okay.
- 大家晚安  - 晚安  马克思
- Good night, fellas. - Good night, Max.
好吧  今晚你值第一班
Okay, you get first shift tonight.
少来了  昨晚我值第一班
Oh, come on, I had it last night.
好吧  别忘了  千万别闭上眼睛
Good, just remember, keep your eyes open.
稍有动静  你得叫醒我  好吗
And one whimper and you wake me up, okay?
- 这里真的很不错  - 你没来过这里
- This is nice. - You've never been here before?
不  我想他们开幕时我还在念书
No, um, I think they opened this when I was at school.
春森市最棒的泰国餐厅
Best Thai food in Springwood.
也是春森市唯一的泰国餐厅
Of course, it's the only Thai food in Springwood.
你爸妈还住在这里吗
Uh, do your parents still live around here?
我妈过世了
My mother passed away.
她在睡梦中断气
She, uh, died in her sleep.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我爸跟我
My father and l, um...
之后我们的生活整个乱了套
Well, things just seemed to fall apart after that.
听起来你应该很不好过
Sounds like a rough time.
没错
It was.
尼尔  如果我告诉你
Neil, what if I told you...
你的病患因为他们的梦身陷险境呢
...that, um, your patients are in real physical danger from their dreams.
恶梦只是真实生活问题的反射
The nightmares are nothing but a symptom of the real problems.
好吧  先暂除排除那样的可能性
All right, well, then let's just eliminate the symptom for the time being.
- 使用去梦眠  - 没错
- With Hypnocil? - That's right.
你要我开
You want me to prescribe...
实验性心理药物给一群有自杀倾向的孩子
...an experimental psychoactive drug to a bunch of suicidal teenagers?
直到我们控制住状况
Just until we get things under control.
去除梦境不是件开玩笑的事
Dream deprivation is nothing to fool around with.
你也不该使用那样的药物
You have no business taking it yourself.
以前我跟他们一样  尼尔  我了解他们的痛苦
I used to be like them, Neil. I know what they're going through.
我也了解
So do l.
你跟我说他们是幸存者  事实的确是如此
You told me they were survivors and they all are.
但他们能撑多久全靠我们了
But how much longer they survive is up to us.
对不起  南希
I'm sorry, Nancy.
答案是不行
The answer is no.
菲利普
Phillip.
菲利普  醒一醒
Phillip, wake up.
祝你梦游愉快  混蛋
Have a nice stroll, asshole.
干嘛  你在做什么
What? What are you doing?
别这样  老兄
Hey, come on, man.
什么  你疯了吗
What, are you crazy?
该死  他在做什么
Oh, shit, what is he doing?
快去找人帮忙  找人帮忙
Get help! Get help!
菲利普  菲利普
Phillip! Phillip!
菲利普  不
Phillip, no!
乔伊
Joey?
怎么了
What's the matter?
菲利普  菲利普
Phillip! Phillip!
菲利普  菲利普  不
Phillip! Phillip, no!
菲利普  不
Phillip, no!
别那么做  不
Don't do it, no!
菲利普  别那么做  菲利普
Phillip, don't do it! Phillip!
该死
Goddamn!
菲利普
Phillip!
- 菲利普  - 菲利普
- Phillip! - Phillip!
- 别跳  - 菲利普  不要跳
- Don't jump! - Phillip, don't jump!
菲利普
Phillip!
- 不要跳 - 啊!
- Don't you jump! - Aah!
我要跟大家谈谈昨晚发生的事
I want us to talk about what happened last night.
我要大家说出自己的感觉
I want us to all get our feelings out in the open.
他不够坚强  所以他死了  就那样
He wasn't strong enough so he got wasted, that's all.
就那样  你是那么想的吗
That's all? Is that what you think?
他无法撑下来  所以他死了
He couldn't hack it so he got nailed, period.
对  超级硬汉  你打算撑多久
Oh, yeah, big, tough bad ass. How long are you gonna last?
我会撑得比你们都久
I'm gonna last longer than any of you.
尽量反抗吧  他就是希望你们能那么做
Well, just go ahead and fight because that's what he wants.
- 谁  - 你觉得是谁呢
- Who? - Who do you think?
他想做什么
What does he want?
他要我们互相残杀  这样才会变得软弱  方便他下手
To turn us against each other so we'll be weak, easy prey.
- 胡说八道  - 不  她是对的
- Horse shit. - No, she's right.
我想大家都没讲到重点
I think we're all missing the point here.
菲利普的死是梦游意外  就那么简单
Phillip's death was a sleepwalking accident, nothing more.
不
No.
我看到他站在上面
I could see him up there.
他的脸
His face...
他一直都是清醒的
He was wide awake all the way down.
这是自杀  菲利普撑不下去  他放弃了
Well, then it was suicide. Phillip quit, he gave up.
乔伊说他不是自杀
Joey says it wasn't suicide.
听我说  乔伊  菲利普是自杀
Listen to me, Joey, Phillip killed himself.
那么做太懦弱了  一点意义都没有
Now, that's a cowardly thing. That's an empty thing.
他让自己失望  也让我们失望
He let himself down. He let all of us down.
那是谋杀  你还不懂吗
It was murder. Can't you understand that?
那个混蛋杀了他
That bastard murdered him!
我不想再听下去
I'm not gonna listen to any more of this.
你们还要将自己的软弱
How much longer are you going to go on...
归咎给恶梦多久
...blaming your dreams for your own weaknesses?
- 你还要指控  - 够了  金凯德
- How much longer you gonna keep throw... - That's enough, Kincaid.
昨晚的意外不能重演
There will be no repeat occurrences of last night's events.
从现在开始  睡觉时你们的房门都得上锁
From now on your doors will be locked during sleeping hours.
我们会在晚上开安眠药给大家吃
We'll start a policy of evening sedation for everybody.
去你的  谁敢对我下药  我一定会揍扁他
he fuck you will. Anybody who tries drugs on me, gets his ass kicked.
今晚你待在禁闭室  孩子
You just bought yourself a night in the quiet room, mister.
- 快坐下  - 去你的  你才要坐下
- Now, sit down. - Fuck you, you sit down.
- 冷静点  金凯德  - 谁都别想叫我睡觉
- Easy, Kincaid. - Nobody is gonna put me to sleep.
离我远一点  别碰我
Get away from me. Leave me alone.
我不要睡觉  谁都别想叫我睡觉
I don't wanna go to sleep. Nobody gonna put me to sleep.
我不要睡觉
I ain't going to sleep!
把你的手  我不要睡觉
Get your hands... I ain't gonna sleep.
待在位置上
Stay in your seats.
把你的手拿开  我不要
Get your hands off me, I don't wanna...
今晚我们得使用安眠药  从他开始
We'll begin sedation tonight starting with him.
你不能那么做  他们会无力对抗恶梦
You can't. They'll be defenseless against their dreams.
他们就是需要那样
That's precisely what they need.
没有打扰地好好睡一觉  会释放出所有负面能量
Some uninterrupted REM sleep to release all that negative energy.
伊莉莎白  我要开去梦眠给他  那是抑制做梦的药物
Elizabeth, I'm prescribing Hypnocil. It's a dream suppressant.
我知道那是什么  我只是不敢相信你会那么说
I know what it is. I just can't believe what I'm hearing.
- 她是怎么说服你的  - 没有
- What has she talked you into? - Nothing.
他们是我的病人  由我来决定
My patients, my decision.
找到答案前  我希望他们不再做梦
I want these dreams stopped till we get some answers.
我不准
I can't allow that.
有必要的话  我会直接去找卡佛
Then I'll go straight to Carver if I have to.
他不支持我  就得批准我的辞呈
And he'll either back me up or accept my resignation.
好吧
All right.
如果出了问题  我要你负起责任
But if something goes wrong, I'll make sure that you're held responsible.
我是说真的  负起全责
I mean that. Fully responsible.
我不敢相信我真的那么说
I can't believe I just said that.
你觉得明天我们能拿到去梦眠吗
Do you think we can get the Hypnocil by tomorrow?
我们得想想办法
We're gonna try.
我希望你知道你帮我们惹上多大的麻烦
I hope you know what you're getting us into.
不再做梦
Ain't gonna dream no more, no more
我不要再做梦
Ain't gonna dream no more
我要整晚唱这首歌
All night long, I sing this song
不要再做梦
Ain't gonna dream no more
- 艾波  - 他拿弹弓打我
- April! - He shot me with a slingshot!
- 我没有  - 骗子
- I did not! - Liar!
- 艾波  - 骗子
- April. - Liar.
别闹了
Hold it, hold it.
- 女孩  你在做什么  - 看电视
- Girl, what are you doing? - Watching TV.
我看得出来
I can see that.
为何不看书  你看太多电视了
Why don't you read a book? You watch too much damn TV.
我在做研究
Research.
对喔  你要当电视明星
Oh, right, you're gonna be a TV star.
等着瞧吧
Wait and see.
对  如果希莫丝发现你熄灯后还待在这里
Yeah, well, if Simms catches you here after lights out,
她会杀了我
she's gonna chew my ass.
- 我得保持清醒  马克思  - 珍妮佛
- I got to stay up, Max. - Jennifer.
只有今晚  求求你
Just tonight, please.
我无法对抗恶梦
I can't handle the nightmare.
菲利普死了  今晚我真的不行
Not after Phillip, not tonight.
好吧
Okay.
但我没看到你
But I never saw you.
- 谢谢你  马克思  - 好吧
- Thanks, Max. - Okay.
这真的太好吃了  布朗太太
This is a great meal, Mrs. Brown...
我吃过最美味的一餐
...really one of the best I've ever had.
谢谢你  史提夫
Thanks, thank you, Steve.
甜心  好消息
Hi, sweet stuff, good news.
你不可能有好消息
It can't be good news coming from you.
我值夜班
I pulled night duty.
- 所以呢  - 这是迈向天堂的钥匙  宝贝
- So? - So got the keys to heaven, baby.
- 什么  - 药局
- What? - The dispensary.
嗑点干净的药  药局大嗨一晚
I am talking clean pharmaceutical high, a night at Club Meth.
- 我不要  - 是吗
- I don't do that shit. - Yeah?
- 那这些是什么  美人痣吗  - 那都过去了
- What are those, beauty marks? - Those are ancient history.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
如果你想重温历史
Well, if you're ever in the mood for a history lesson...
我可以当你的老师  懂吗
... I'm your teacher, understand?
快滚开  不然我会去跟马克思报告
Stay out of my face or I'll go straight to Max.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
谁会相信你这种吸毒的疯女人呢
Now, who's gonna take the word of a crazy junkie chick like you?
滚开
Fuck off!
甜心  我以为  今晚你会去看我打保龄球
Hon, I kind of figured you'd watch me bowl tonight.
我们要卫冕喔
We're defending the championship, you know?
- 我们  - 待会儿我们可能会过去
- Oh, we 're... - Maybe we 'll come by later.
我想  大家要离开了  大概不会想吃甜点吧
Don 't suppose anybody would like some dessert before they leave.
- 不了  谢谢  妈  - 不了  晚餐很好吃
- No, thanks, Mom. - No, it was very good.
- 谢谢  - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thanks.
海伦
Helen? Hmm?
你跟她谈过问题了吗
Have you, you know, talked to her about the way things are?
多年前我就谈过了
Years ago.
多年前
Years?
为什么我要跟老太婆见面
What do I want to see an old barn for?
- 少来了  那真的很浪漫 - 啊 嗯
- Come on, it's romantic. - Aah! U nh.
听我说  艾波
Look, April.
你要拿回你的车钥匙  对不对
You want your car keys back, don 't you?
这么问或许很蠢  他们得杀多少条才够
...silly thing to ask you, but how many of what did they have to kill?
别这么说  我热爱动物
Don't say that because I love animals.
我去过动物收容所
I've seen animal shelters.
我只买了红色带黑的  所以不知道到底是什么东西
I bought it only red with black in it, so I didn't know what it was.
- 或许是人工鸟的羽毛 - 哈
- Probably from an artificial bird. - Ha.
你上过演员训练班吗
Did you ever go to any kind of acting school?
一开始没有  我从脱口秀起家
Not in the beginning. I started on a talk show.
如果有年轻女演员问你"你是如何成功的"
When a young actress says, "How do you succeed in this?"
- 你不会要她们去念书吧  - 念书
- You don 't always say study? - Study.
我觉得念书很重要
I think you should study.
她们得念书  再投入职场
They have to study, work.
或许就有机会成功
And then maybe you can make it.
- 我能问你一个问题吗  - 当然可以
- Can I ask you something? - Certainly.
你以为你哪根葱
Who gives a fuck what you think?
这是你的机会  珍妮佛
This is your break, Jennifer.
一  二
One, two
佛莱迪要来抓你了
Freddy's coming for you
三  四
Three, four
锁好你的门
Better lock your door
这是你的机会  珍妮佛
This is your break, Jennifer.
这是你的机会  珍
This is your break, Jen...
- 没错  珍妮佛  你上电视的大好机会 - 啊!
- This is it, Jennifer, your big break in TV. - Aah!
- 欢迎来到黄金时段  贱人 - 啊!
- Welcome to prime time, bitch! - Aah!
别觉得丢脸  年轻人
Don't be ashamed, young man.
这里本来就是个悲伤的地方
This is a place for sorrow.
你信哪一种宗教
What faith do you follow?
我想我只相信科学
Science, I suppose.
很悲伤的选择
Sad choice.
有时候那无法提供安慰
There are times when it doesn't offer much comfort.
我见过你吗  修女
I've seen you before, uh, Sister.
玛丽·海伦娜
Mary Helena.
你在医院当义工
You do volunteer work at the hospital.
有时候  如果他们需要我
From time to time, when I'm needed.
我应该可以救他们的
I should have been able to save them.
只有一个办法能救孩子们
Only one thing can save the children.
必须让那个骚动的鬼魂安息
The unquiet spirit must be laid to rest.
他让人神共愤
It is an abomination to God and to man.
尼尔
Neil.
对不起  修女
Excuse me, Sister.
你来这里做什么
What are you doing up here?
我跟
Uh, I was just talking to...
谁
To who?
那不重要
Doesn't matter.
- 你要走了吗  - 当然
- Are you ready to go now? - Sure.
你吃饱了吗
Are you finished?
对  抱歉  我想我不饿
Yeah, I'm sorry. I guess l, uh... I'm not hungry.
没关系
That's okay.
这很漂亮  这是什么
That's pretty. What is it?
这是我的马来西亚梦娃娃
This is my Malaysian dream doll.
应该能带来美梦
It's supposed to bring good dreams.
现在我们的确需要美梦
Could use some of that right about now.
以前我总认为
You know, I used to think...
我可以为孩子们做一些事  改变他们的生活
... I could do something for the kids, make some kind of difference.
但是现在他们一个一个消失了
But they're slipping through my fingers, every one of them.
你尽力在帮他们  尼尔
You're doing the best you can for them, Neil.
是吗
Am l?
我找不到答案
I'm running out of answers.
梦游病人在高度戒备病房跳楼身亡
A patient sleepwalks out of a high-security ward.
单独待在房里的女孩死了
A girl alone in a room dies.
我不敢相信这是真的
I can't believe this is happening.
完全没有逻辑可言
Nothing makes any sense.
那么或许你已经准备好了
Then maybe you're ready.
准备好什么
For what?
真相
The ruth.
告诉我吧
Try me.
如果你愿意放下你所学的一切  真的相信我
Only if you're willing to put aside everything you've learned and trust me.
你做得到吗
Can you do that?
我做得到
I can do that.
好吧
Okay.
在这里我们得直言不讳
Straight talk only in this room.
这是团体治疗吗
Is this group?
对  非正式治疗
Well, yeah, unofficially.
很快地我们的人数就不足以做团体治疗
Pretty soon, there won't be enough of us left to call it "group."
好吧  听着  各位
Okay, listen up, you guys.
南希有话要说
Nancy has something to say.
我知道谁想杀了你们
I know who's trying to kill you.
别跟我们开玩笑  我们没那个心情
Don't humor us. We're not in the mood.
他戴着肮脏的棕色帽子
He wears a dirty, brown hat.
皮肤严重烧伤
He's horribly burned.
他的右手跟利刃一样
He has razors on his right hand.
他是谁
Who is he?
他叫佛莱迪·克鲁格
His name is Freddy Krueger.
死前是个专杀孩童的凶手
He was a child murderer before he died.
他死后
And after he died...
变成了厉鬼
...well, he became something worse.
六年前他杀了我的朋友
Six years ago, he killed my friends.
他差点杀了我
He almost killed me.
他为什么要追杀我们
Why is he after us?
对啊  我们做了什么
Yeah, what did we do?
问题不在你们身上
It's not you.
你们的爸妈跟我的爸妈将他活活烧死
Your parents, my parents, they burned him alive.
现在我们得为他们做的事付出代价
And now we're paying for their sins.
你们是最后一批榆树街儿童
You are the last of the Elm Street children.
我爸跟我妈
Mom and Dad?
那太疯狂了  他们从来没跟我提过这件事
I mean, that's crazy. They never mentioned anything...
是喔  爸妈的确会跟孩子提这种事
Oh, sure, that's the sort of thing parents tell their kids.
"晚安  宝贝  快祷告吧
"Good night, darling, say your prayers.
对了  你爸跟我昨晚烧死一个疯子"
And, oh, by the way, your father and I torched some maniac last night."
我们该怎么对付这个怪物
So what do we do about this creep?
克莉丝丹是关键人物
Kristen is the key.
她有非常特别的天赋
She has a very special talent, a gift.
我长大后就无法那么做
I haven't been able to do that since I was a little girl.
那晚你就做到了
You did it the other night.
那不一样
That was different.
你不可能失去那样的天赋  你只是忘记如何使用
You never lose a gift like that. You just forget how to use it
你何不试试看呢
How about it, will you try?
你们都有这样的心灵力量
All of you have this inner strength.
在最美的梦里拥有的特殊力量
Some special power that you've had in your most wonderful dreams.
我们可以一起试着使用那样的力量
Together, we can learn to use that power if we try.
你的口气很像彼得潘
You sound like Peter Pan.
记得吗  保持心胸开阔
Remember, open mind.
好吧
Okay.
泰纶  麻烦你将窗帘拉上
Uh, Taryn, would you pull the shades down please?
我们来做团体催眠
We're gonna try a little, uh, group hypnosis.
我要你们注视这个钟摆
I want you all to follow this pendulum with your eyes.
抛开其他的杂念
Tune out everything else.
注视着钟摆
Nothing else exists but the pendulum.
带我们到那里去  克莉丝丹
Take us there, Kristen.
深呼吸  放轻松
Breathe deeply and relax.
从脚趾开始
Starting with your toes,
放松一切  让身体不再感到紧张
relax everything till there's no tension left in your bodies.
持续注视着钟摆
Keep following the pendulum.
你们会发现自己累了
You find yourselves getting tired.
现在真的很想
Nothing would feel better right now...
好好深深地睡一觉
...than a nice, long, deep sleep.
我要从五开始倒数
I'm gonna count backwards from five.
倒数完毕
When I finish...
你们都会睡着
...you will all be asleep.
四
Four.
三
Three.
二
Two.
一
One.
抱歉
Sorry.
没关系  我们可以再试一次
That's okay, we'll try again.
休息一下
Everybody take five. Ahem.
我愿意这么做  让孩子们跟你觉得安心
I was willing to go through with this for the kids' peace of mind and yours...
但你得面对现实
...but you're gonna have to face reality.
不  我是说真的  我很容易被催眠
No, I'm serious, I happen to be very susceptible to hypnosis.
- 专业人士是那么跟我说的  - 什么专业人士
- I've been told by professionals. - What professionals?
那些专业人士在哪里
Where are these professionals?
我指的专业人士是魔术师跟幻术家
Well, "professionals" as in, like, magic-users and illusionists.
听着  乔伊  我只是想跟你独处一下
Listen, Joey, I just wanted to get you alone for a second.
听我说  我真的很喜欢你
I mean, look, I really like you.
你喜欢我吗
Do you like me?
我知道这听起来很夸张
I know this sounds crazy...
但是我每天编藉口到病房看你
...but I make up excuses to come into the ward every day just to see you.
你真的好可爱
You're so cute.
尼尔  我们得再试一次
Neil, let's just try one more time.
如果还是不行  我保证我会
If it doesn't work, I promise I'll...
我们到了
We're here.
到了哪里
Where here?
我们进入梦境里
We're in the dream.
不  不可能  我们还在团体治疗室里
Well, no, we're not. We're still here in the group.
在梦里我会走路
In my dreams, I can walk.
我的腿非常有力
My legs are strong.
在梦里我是大法师
In my dreams, I am the wizard master.
试试看  克莉丝丹  在梦里你可以做什么
Try something, Kristen. What can you do in your dream?
满分  观众为之疯狂
A perfect score. The crowd goes wild. Ahh!
- 哈哈 - 该死  看我的厉害
- Ha, ha! - Fucking A, dig this.
金凯德  拜托
Kincaid, please.
那让人很不安
That's very unnerving.
你们快看泰纶
Hey, check out Taryn.
在梦里我是个美女
In my dreams, I'm beautiful...
也是个坏女孩
...and bad.
听着  我这么做会惹上大麻烦
Look, I could get into a lot of trouble for this.
但我知道你不会说的  对吧
But I know you won't say anything, will you?
帮我拉开拉链
Unzip me.
你喜欢我的身材吗  乔伊
Do you like my body, Joey?
怎么了  乔伊
What's wrong, Joey?
舌头打结了吗
Feeling tongue-tied?
发生了什么事
What's happening?
- 他在附近  - 谁
- He's close. - Who?
- 是佛莱迪吗  - 他在走廊
- Freddy? - He's out in the halls.
- 乔伊在哪里  - 佛莱迪抓走他了
- Where's Joey? - Freddy's got him.
大家安静  你们听
Quiet, everyone, listen.
房间变了
The room's changing.
到底发生了什么事
What the heck is going on?
- 医生  - 发生了什么事
- Doctor... - What's happening?
离墙边远一点
Get away from the wall!
别慌张  安静点
Don't panic! Quiet down!
救命啊  救命啊
Help! Help!
- 这不是真的  - 哥登医生
- This isn't real! - Dr. Gordon!
- 不  - 不可能
- No! - It's not!
安静  你们看门
Quiet, the door.
发生了什么事
What's going on in here?
乔伊怎么了
What's wrong with Joey?
乔伊
Joey.
- 蓝色警报  - 天啊
- Code blue. - Oh, my God.
他陷入重度昏迷  我们没办法治好他
He's in a deep coma. There's nothing we can do for him.
这令人无法原谅
This is inexcusable.
治疗并未经过授权
The session was unauthorized.
在我不知情的状况下进行
It was purposely conducted without my knowledge.
卡佛医生  我们得采取必要行动
Unusual steps were called for, Dr. Carver.
我该把你的话  转告给那孩子的爸妈吗
Is that what I should tell that young man's parents?
我了解你开实验性药物
I understand you prescribed a highly experimental drug.
卡佛医生  他并非陷入昏迷  因为
Dr. Carver, he's not in a coma because of...
小女孩  我不想听你的意见
Young lady, your opinion is of no interest to me.
而且根据希莫丝医生的说法
Furthermore, according to Dr. Simms...
你一直在引发病人的恐慌
...you've been creating panic among the patients.
- 那不是真的  - 哥登医生
- That's not true. - Dr. Gordon.
四天来有两名病人自杀
In the last four days, we've had two suicides.
现在那个孩子陷入昏迷
Now that young man is in a coma.
我相信我们可以说  你的方法完全失败
I think it's safe to say that your approach has failed, entirely.
你们两个都被解职了  我要你们今天就离开这里
You're both relieved of duty. I want you out of here today.
对不起  尼尔  不过我恐怕这是你自找的
I'm sorry, Neil. I'm afraid you brought it on yourself.
天啊  伊莉莎白  拜托  拜托你试着帮这些孩子
For God's sake, Elizabeth, please. Will you please just try to help the kids?
你能听他们说话吗
Will you listen to them?
我当然会的
Of course, I will.
我们该怎么办
What are we going to do?
我们一点办法都没有  现在我们帮不上忙
There is nothing that we can do. It's out of our hands.
修女
Sister!
Sister?
有人在吗
Hello?
修女
Sister?
一切都是从这里开始的
This is where it began.
这一区已经封闭多年
This wing has been closed for years.
以前这是什么地方
What was this place?
炼狱
Purgatory.
人们一手打造出来的
Fashioned by the hands of men.
扭曲寂寞的灵魂
Twisted, lonely souls.
最可怕的疯狂罪犯
The worst of the criminally insane...
跟动物一样被关在这里
...were locked up in here like animals.
这里在四零年代被封闭了  不是吗
This whole facility was shut down in the '40s, wasn't it?
好像是因为有丑闻
Some sort of scandal?
有个年轻的女性工作人员
A young girl on the staff...
放假时不小心被关在这里
...was accidentally locked in here over the holidays.
病人将她藏起来好几天
The inmates kept her hidden for days.
她不断地被强暴
She was raped hundreds of times.
他们发现她时  她已经奄奄一息
When they found her, she was barely alive...
而且怀孕了
...and with child.
那女孩是亚曼达·克鲁格
That girl was Amanda Krueger.
- 她的孩子  - 佛莱迪
- Her child... - Freddy.
一堆疯子生下的私生子
The bastard son of a hundred maniacs.
有人说他遭到杀害
Some say he was murdered...
但一直没有找到尸体
...though no body was ever found.
之前你提到要让他安息
You said something before about laying him to rest.
你得找到他的遗骸
You must find the remains...
在圣地火化
...and bury him in hallowed ground.
圣地
Hallowed ground?
修女
Sister?
如果你只相信科学  医生
If your only faith is science, doctor...
或许该安息的人是你
...it may be you that's laid to rest.
等一下  修女
Wait! Sister!
放了他  你这个混蛋
Let go of him, you bastard.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我必须进入梦境  我们别无选择
I've got to go in. We don't have a choice.
害自己没命救不了那些孩子
Getting yourself killed won't help the kids at all.
而且我们有选择
Besides, we do have a choice.
如果你幻想中的修女说的没错
Well, assuming your mysterious nun is right.
这星期我听过更奇怪的事
I've heard weirder things this week.
好吧
All right.
不论她是谁  她似乎比我更了解克鲁格
Whoever she is, she does seem to know more about Krueger than I do.
问题是他的尸体到底在哪里
The question is, what happened to his body?
他们在他的锅炉室烧死他  把他的遗骸藏起来
They burned him to death in his boiler room and they hid the remains.
谁有可能知道遗骸藏在哪里
Who would know where they're hidden?
只有一个人知道
Well, only one man knows.
现在他一定得开口了
And it's time for him to talk.
不
No!
你不能把南希赶走
You can't take Nancy away from us!
你不能那么做  她是唯一能帮我们的人
You can't! She's all we have!
你病了  克莉丝丹
You're a sick girl, Kristen.
你想好起来  就得信任我
If you wanna get better, you must trust me now.
不
No!
- 不  - 带她去禁闭室  帮她注射镇定剂
- No, no! - Take her to the quiet room and sedate her.
- 别激动  - 你这个笨贱人  你会害死我们的
- Take it easy. - You stupid bitch, you're killing us!
你会害死我们的
You're killing us!
不
No!
你会害死我们的
You're killing us!
不
No!
好了  大伙儿们  该睡了
All right, everybody, back to bed.
不  不
No! No!
爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
原来是我的宝贝女儿
Well, if it isn't my little girl.
我的心肝来看爸爸了
My baby come to see her daddy, huh?
- 好久不见了  - 对啊
- It's been a long time. - Yeah.
但你来了  坐吧
But you're here, sit down.
你来找我有什么事
What did I do to, uh, get so lucky?
我以为你试着想忘记我
I thought that you were trying to forget me.
那不是真的  想要遗忘的人是你
That's not true. You're the one who's trying to forget.
少来了
Oh, come on.
我需要你帮忙  爸爸
I need your help, Dad.
克鲁格回来了
Krueger is back.
佛莱迪·克鲁格死了
Fred Krueger is dead.
你一直无法了解那一点  甜心
You always had a little trouble trying to understand that, sweetheart.
你知道他做了什么
You know what he did.
他故技重施
He's doing it again.
我想我们没见过面  朋友
I don't believe we've ever met, friend.
而且这完全不关你的事
And I don't think this is any of your goddamn business.
我认为这次我们能阻止他  让他永远不会回来
I think we can stop him this time. Stop him for good.
但我们得知道  他的遗骸藏在哪里
But we need to know where his bones were hidden.
这件事让我失去太多
I've lost too much over this already.
我不干了
I'm through with it.
过了这么久  还有人为此丢掉性命
People are still dying after all this time.
别再逃避了
Stop running away from it.
这是你欠我的
You owe me.
很高兴能再见到你  小公主
It was nice seeing you again, princess.
下次早一点来找我
Next time, don't stay away so long.
南希
Nancy?
- 南希  - 我没事  给我一点时间
- Nancy. - I'll be okay, just give me a minute.
是医院找我
That's the hospital.
- 哥登医生  - 泰纶
- Dr. Gordon? - Taryn?
你得立刻赶过来  是克莉丝丹  她严重失控
You've got to come right away. It's Kristen, she had a total shit attack.
希莫丝帮她注射镇定剂  还把她关在禁闭室
Simms doped her up, put her in the quiet room.
希莫丝将克莉丝丹关在禁闭室过夜  还帮她注射镇定剂
Simms put Kristen in the quiet room for the night. They sedated her.
不会吧
Oh, no.
她无法保持清醒太久  她一个人被关在里面
She can't stay awake for long. She's all alone in there.
佛莱迪会对她下手
Freddy is gonna get her.
好  大家别慌张  保持冷静
Okay, none of you panic, just stay cool.
救兵立刻赶到
Help is on the way.
- 快一点  - 好吧
- Just hurry. - Okay.
- 我们得立刻赶过去  - 你去吧  我得去找遗骸
- We better get there now. - You go, I gotta get the remains.
- 这是没有用的  - 我会跟他谈的  你去医院
- It's no use. You see him. - I'll talk, you get to the hospital.
- 试着说服希莫丝  - 她不会相信的
- Make Simms understand. - She'll never.
我得去救克莉丝丹
I got to get to Kristen somehow.
南希  小心一点
Nancy, be careful.
我是尼尔·哥登  幸会
My name is Neil Gordon. Pleased to meet you.
好  我们正式介绍过了
There, now we've met.
听我说
Now, listen to me!
我不知道你在不在乎南希的死活  但我在乎
I don't know if you care whether Nancy lives or dies but I do!
你跟我去找遗骸
You and I are going on a little scavenger hunt.
求求祢  上帝
Please, God.
别让我睡着
Don't make me sleep.
我们来这里做什么
What the hell are we doing here?
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey!
我很快就出来
I won't be long.
- 你以为你在做什么 - 呃…
- What do you think you're doing? - Uh...
听着  对不起
Look, uh, sorry. Heh.
我真的需要这个  我
I really need this. I got, uh...
我会赔偿你
I'll reimburse you.
来吧  我把驾照押在这里  我会回来的
Here, you can keep my driver's license. I'll be back.
马克思  我要见克莉丝丹
Max, I need to see Kristen.
你不了解
You don't understand.
汤普森小姐  省省力气吧  希莫丝医生下了命令
Look, Miss Thompson, save your breath. Dr. Simms gave me specific instructions.
谁都不能见克莉丝丹  特别是你
No one gets to see Kristen, especially you.
马克思  她需要我  她有危险  你得相信我
But Max, she needs me, she's in danger. You got to believe me.
听着  我相信你是好意  但这些孩子差点没命
Listen, I really think you mean well, I do. But my kids have been dying off.
就算没有希莫丝的命令
And even if I didn't have orders from Simms...
我也不会让你靠近她  不可能
...I wouldn't let you near her, no way.
好吧  马克思  我了解
Okay, Max, I understand.
- 我能跟其他孩子道别吗  - 不知道
- Can I say goodbye to the others? - I don't know.
这是我的最后机会
It will be my last chance.
好吧  给你五分钟  他们在视厅室
Okay, you got five minutes. They're in the TV room.
你跑到哪里去了  我们急到快发疯了
Where have you been? We've been going crazy.
- 没时间多说  来吧  - 去哪里
- Shh! There's no time for that, come on. - Where?
最后一次团体治疗
Our last group.
好吧
All right.
就在那里
In there.
我们知道在那里  谁都无法找到遗骸
We knew nobody would ever find it in that place.
连我都不确定我能不能找到
I'm not sure I can find it myself anymore.
(潘尼兄弟废车厂)
好吧  遗骸就藏在废车厂里
All right, it's deep in the heart of the place.
慢慢来
Take it slow.
在这里只能直言不讳
Straight talk only in here.
克莉丝丹怎么了
What about Kristen?
我们无法接近她  我试过了
We can't get to her, I tried.
可惜没有时间  学会怎么利用梦镜
I was hoping we would have more time to learn to use the dreams.
乔伊陷在梦境里
But Joey is in there.
不论有没有我们  莉丝丹会进入梦境里
And Kristen is going in with or without us.
他们需要我们
They need us.
你是说我们可以进入梦境找她  跟她合作
You mean, we're gonna try to go in with her? To link up?
这是唯一的机会
It's now or never.
我不会跟你们开玩笑  这么做真的很危险
I'm not gonna kid you. This is as dangerous as it gets.
如果你们在这个梦境里死了  是真的会没命
If you die in this dream, it's for real.
如果不愿意  可以不用加入
Nobody has to go in that doesn't want to.
我要加入
I'm in.
我也是
Me too.
我们得进入梦境修理这个家伙
Let's go kick the motherfucker's ass all over dreamland.
- 太棒了 - 哈哈
- Yeah. - Ha, ha.
记住  不论发生什么事  我们不可以走散
So remember, we have to stay together whatever happens.
只有那样才能打败他
It's the only way we can beat him.
好  现在你们得放空
All right, clear your mind of everything.
想像自己在禁闭室里
Picture yourself in the quiet room...
柔和的白色墙壁  一片寂静
...the soft white walls, the total silence.
只能听到自己的心跳声
Only the sound of your heart beating.
想像你们跟克莉丝丹在那里
Picture yourself there with Kristen.
我要从五开始倒数
I'm gonna count backwards from five.
倒数完毕  我们都会睡着
And when I'm done, we'll all be asleep.
我们会一起出现在禁闭室里
We'll all be in the quiet room.
五
Five.
四
Four.
三
Three.
二
Two.
一
One.
南希  我就知道你会来
Nancy, heh, I knew you would come.
你以为我们会抛弃你吗
You don't think we'd let you go in alone, do you?
- 不可能  我们是一支团队  - 对
- No way, we are a team. - Yeah.
听着  各位  乔伊需要我们  我能感觉到他
Listen, everybody, Joey needs us. I can feel him.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我们该怎么找到他  克莉丝丹
How do we find him, Kristen?
待在房间中央
Stay in the middle of the room!
不论发生什么事  别走散了
No matter what happens, stay together!
- 救命啊  - 南希
- Help! - Nancy!
救救我
Help me!
甜心  你会吵醒邻居的
Honey, you're gonna wake up the whole neighborhood.
你怎么还没睡  已经一点多了
What are you still doing up? It's past 1.
我
I...
我想等你回来
I just thought I'd wait for you.
我回来了  你该去睡觉
Well, I'm home. You can get to sleep now.
快点  动作快
Come on, Andale.
你是在做什么
What's that for?
我很高兴你回来了
I'm just glad you're home.
妈  我做了好可怕的恶梦
Mom, I had the most awful dream.
伊莲  波本威士忌放在哪里
Elaine, where do you keep the bourbon?
我立刻下去
I'll be right down.
克莉丝  我有客人
Kris, I've got a guest.
拜托  妈妈  我不想一个人
Please, Mom, I just don't wanna be alone.
啊
Aah!
- 我问你波本威士忌放在哪里  - 妈
- I said, where is the fucking bourbon! - Mom!
你该听你妈妈的话
You should listen to your mother.
该死  克莉丝丹  什么都你毁了
Goddamn it, Kristen, you ruin everything.
每次我带男人回家你就搞破坏
Every time I bring a man home, you spoil it!
你知道心理医生是怎么说的  你只是想引人注意
You know what your shrink says, you're just trying to get attention!
南希
Nancy!
克莉丝丹
Kristen!
是你吗
Is that you?
欢迎你回来  泰纶
Welcome home, Taryn.
看起来很眼熟吧
Look familiar?
好  混蛋  我们一决高下
Okay, asshole, let's dance.
泰纶  泰纶  泰纶
Taryn, Taryn, Taryn.
我们为什么要互相残杀
Why? Why should we fight?
你跟我是老朋友  记得吗
We're old friends, you and l, remember?
我们来茫一下吧
Let's get high.
这真的是太骇了
What a rush.
有人在吗
Hello?
大伙儿  你们在哪里
You guys, where are you?
有人在吗
Is somebody there?
威尔
Oh, Will.
你似乎累了
You look tired.
坐吧
Have a seat.
不  谢谢  我这样就好
No, thanks. I'm fine just the way I am.
或许你暂时可以
For now maybe.
但清醒之后
But when you wake up...
你又得去坐轮椅
...it's back in the saddle again.
我的腿
My leg!
你的轮椅来了  孩子
It's the chair for you, kid.
我是大法师
I am the wizard master.
I am the wizard master!
以精灵王子罗雷克之名  魔鬼快快退去
In the name of Lowrek, Prince of Elves, demon, begone.
抱歉  孩子  我不相信童话故事
Sorry, kid. I don't believe in fairy tales.
哈罗
Hello?
有人在吗
Somebody?
哈罗
Hello.
- 克莉丝丹  - 南希
- Kristen! - Nancy! Aah!
- 那是怎么一回事  - 不知道
- What is that? - I don't know.
我就知道你们在这里
Yo, I thought I heard voices.
金凯德  我该亲亲你的
Kincaid, I could kiss you.
- 当然可以啊 - 嗯
- What's stopping you? - Mm!
酷啊  乔伊在哪里
Cool. So where's Joey?
不知道  这里跟迷宫差不多
I don't know. This place is Iike a maze.
那么别再猜了  我们得大展身手
Then it's time to stop guessing and start messing.
唷  佛莱迪
Yo, Freddy!
你躲在哪里  丑八怪
Where you hiding, you burnt-face pussy?
我们应该先去找其他人
Hey, we should find the others first.
你以为你抓走那个哑巴  是件很光荣的事吗
You think you're hot shit with a mute kid, don't you?
让我看看你能不能对付我
Well, let me see you come get a piece of me.
克鲁格  胆小鬼
Krueger! Pussy!
我就知道他是个胆小鬼
I knew he was a little chicken.
该死
Shit.
是一扇门
It's a door.
但后面是死路一条
But it doesn't go anywhere.
不  不是那样的
Yes, it does.
就是这里
This is it.
你们准备好了吗
Are you ready?
我们得去除掉那个混蛋
Let's snuff the sucker.
就是这里
That's it.
就是那辆凯迪拉克
The Caddy.
你要去哪里
Going somewhere?
听着  我说过  我会告诉你遗骸藏在哪里
Look, I said I'd show you where the goddamn thing was.
- 我可没说我会留下来  - 我们有很多工作要做
- I never said I'd stick around. - We've got work to do.
- 你在胡说什么  - 你得参加一场葬礼
- What are you talking about? - You're about to attend a funeral.
一场迟来的葬礼
One that's long overdue.
乔伊
Joey!
Joey.
你看  小宝贝们回来了
Look, all the little piggies come home.
放了他  克鲁格
Let him go, Krueger!
遵命
Your wish is my command.
- 不  - 乔伊
- No! - Joey!
南希
Nancy.
他很强壮  他从来没有这么强壮过
He's strong. He's never been this strong.
没错
Yes, sir.
孩子的灵魂给了我力量
The souls of the children give me strength.
- 不 - 啊
- No. - Unh.
我一向是来者不拒
Always room for more.
- 那是什么声音  - 什么
- What's that? - What?
注意听
Listen.
这里还有别人
Somebody else is out here.
不
No.
这里只有我们
We're alone.
把这该死的家伙埋了
Bury the fucking thing!
真的是你
It's really you.
我曾杀过你  你这个混蛋
I killed you once before, you son of a bitch.
我们得往这边走
Let's try this way.
克莉丝丹  你能让我们脱离梦境吗
Kristen, can you pull us out?
他们帮我注射镇定剂  我们被困在这里了
They sedated me. We're stuck here.
前面没路
It's a dead end.
搞什么
What the hell?
抱歉让你们久等
Sorry to keep you waiting.
或许我该好好地招待你们一下
Perhaps if there was more of me to spread around.
不
No!
哇  我真的那么说了
Wow, did I say that?
你找到你的美梦力量了  兄弟
You found your dream power, man.
你救了我们  乔伊
You saved us, Joey.
- 你吓跑他了  - 放我下去
- Man, you blew him away. - Put me down, man.
- 你没事吧  - 应该没事
- Are you okay? - I think so.
他离开了
He's gone.
一切都结束了
It's over. Ha, ha.
南希
Nancy.
爸爸
Daddy?
我跨过边界来见你  小公主
I've crossed over, princess.
跨过边界
Crossed over?
离开前得告诉你  我为我所做过的事感到抱歉
I couldn't go without telling you how sorry I am for all the things I've done.
我非常爱你
I love you so much.
我会永远爱你
I'll always love you.
你死定了
Die.
南希
Nancy.
现在你是我的了  小女孩
You're mine now, little piggy!
- 不  - 啊 啊
- No! - Unh, agh!
求求你  上帝  为了那些孩子跟南希
Please, God, for the children, for Nancy.
尘归尘
Ashes to ashes.
土归土
Dust to dust.
让他的灵魂安息吧
May the spirit rest.
我不会让你死的  我不会让你死的
I won't let you die. I won't let you.
我要带你进入美梦
I'm gonna dream you into a beautiful dream...
直到永远
...forever and ever.
你们众民当时时倚靠他
Trust in him at all times, O people.
在你面前倾心吐意  神是我们的避难所
Pour out your hearts to him, for God is our refuge.
神啊  求你听我的呼求  侧耳听我的祷告
Hear my cry, O God. Listen to my prayer.
我心里发昏的时候
From the ends of the earth, I call to you.
我要从地极求告祢
I call as my heart grows faint.
求你领我到那比我更高的磐石
Lead me to the rock that is higher than I.
因为你作过我的避难所
For you have been my refuge.
作过我的坚固台  脱离仇敌
A strong tower against the foe.
我要永远住在你的帐幕里
I long to dwell in the tent forever
我要投靠在你翅膀下的隐密处
and take refuge in the shelter of your wings.
即使我们安葬了南希  她的勇气跟精神与我们同在
Even though we entrust Nancy to the earth,
她的勇气跟精神与我们同在
her courage and spirit shall remain with us.
因为安慰我们的上帝说
For the Lord, God, has comforted us saying...
凡是想救自己生命的  必丧掉生命
that whoever finds his life will lose it...
但为我牺牲生命的  必得着生命
and whoever loses his life for my sake will find it.
他们将永远活在天国的荣光里
They shall live forever in the glory of his kingdom.
愿上帝保佑  降福于你们
May the Lord bless you and keep you.
愿神使他的脸光照你  赐恩给你
May the Lord make his face to shine down upon you and be gracious to you.
愿神向你仰脸  赐你平安
May the Lord turn his face toward you and give you peace.
天啊
My God.
你是他的妈妈
You were his mother.